Street & Smith Records
Street & Smith Records
- Scripts
  - Nick Carter
    - no. 166 The Case of the Son's Confession, 12 Feb 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. [167] The Case of the Unimportant Murder, 19 Feb 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 168 The Case of the Painted Heel, 26 Feb 1950; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 169 The Case of the Thirteenth Clue, 5 Mar 1950; 29 pp. (Box 327)
    - no. 170 The Case of the Short Blonde Hair, 12 Mar 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 171 The Case of the Hot Rod Murder, 19 Mar 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 172 The Case of the Beggars' League, 26 Mar 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 173 The Case of the Reluctant Witness, 2 Apr 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 174 The Case of the Big Key, 9 Apr 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 175 The Case of the Guilty Corpse, 16 Apr 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 176 The Case of the Murderers' Haven, 23 Apr 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. [177] The Case of the Purple Tiger, 30 Apr 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 178 The Case of the Murder for Charity, 7 May 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 179 The Case of the Greedy Ghost, 14 May 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 327)
    - no. 180 The Case of the Hypnotic Hostess, 21 May 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 181 The Case of the Hole in the Wall, 28 May 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 182 The Case of the Purloined Arrow, 4 Jun 1950; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 183 The Case of the Dead Client, 11 Jun 1950; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 184 The Case of the Kindergarten Murders, 18 Jun 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 185 The Case of the Purple Clue, 25 Jun 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 186 The Case of the Penny Arcade Murder, 2 Jul 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 187 The Case of the Corpse Who Changed His Mind, 9 Jul 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 188 The Case of the Murder Dreamer, 16 Jul 1950; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 189 The Case of the Sleeper Murders, 23 Jul 1950; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 190 Case of the Restless Corpse, 30 Jul 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 191 The Case of the Twice-Murdered Man, 6 Aug 1950; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 192 The Case of the Jealous Pitcher, 13 Aug 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 193 The Case of the Greedy Thieves, 20 Aug 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 328)
    - no. 194 The Case of the Murder Frame, 27 Aug 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 195 The Case of the Misled Skeletons, 3 Sep 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 196 The Case of the Broken Glasses, 10 Sep 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 197 The Case of the Little Grey Man, 17 Sep 1950; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 198 The Case of the High Note Murder, 24 Sep 1950; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 199 The Case of the Waiting Murder, 1 Oct 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 200 The Case of the Olgari Curse, 8 Oct 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 201 The Case of the Deadly Diamonds, 15 Oct 1950; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 202 The Case of the Phantom Fortune, 22 Oct 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 203 The Case of the Careful Killer, 29 Oct 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 204 The Case of the Foolproof Murder, 5 Nov 1950; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 205 The Case of the Murder Marathon, 12 Nov 1950; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 206 The Case of the Peculiar Penthouse, 19 Nov 1950; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 207 The Case of the Baffling Bullets, 26 Nov 1950; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 329)
    - no. 208 The Case of the Dead Dummy, 3 Dec 1950; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 209 The Case of the Lovelorn Letter, 10 Dec 1950; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 210 The Case of the Last Survivor, 17 Dec 1950; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. [211] The Case of the Sinister Santa Claus, 18 Dec 1950; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 212 The Case of the Wrong Murder, 31 Dec 1950; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 213 The Case of the Vanished Loot, 7 Jan 1951; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 214 The Case of the Million Dollar Motive, 14 Jan 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 215 The Case of the Necessary Corpse, 21 Jan 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 216 The Case of the Pock-Marked Thumbnail, 28 Jan 1951; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 217 The Case of the Bewildered Beauty, 4 Feb 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 218 The Case of the Hitch-Hike Killer, 11 Feb 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 219 The Case of the Old Man's Darling, 18 Feb 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 220 The Case of the Vanished Villain, 25 Feb 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 221 The Case of the Horror Hotel, 4 Mar 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 222 The Case of the Innocent Killer, 11 Mar 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 330)
    - no. 223 The Case of the Confused Bystander, 18 Mar 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 224 The Case of the Gangster's Bride, 25 Mar 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 225 The Case of the Misunderstood Merchant, 1 Apr 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 226 The Case of the Golden Hand, 8 Apr 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 227 The Case of the Wealthy Widow, 15 Apr 1951; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 228 The Case of the Triple Identity, 22 Apr 1951; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 229 The Case of the Fabulous Fraud, 29 Apr 1951; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 230 The Case of the Terrified Swami, 6 May 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 231 The Case of the Murder Mansion, 13 May 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 232 The Case of the Punchboard Murder, 20 May 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 233 The Case of the Gentle Killers, 27 May 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 234 The Case of the Innocent Lifer, 3 Jun 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 235 The Case of the Peculiar Puzzle, 10 Jun 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 236 The Case of the Unmarked Snow, 17 Jun 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 237 The Case of the Fraudulent Fires, 24 Jun 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 331)
    - no. 238 The Case of the Frightened Ghost, 1 Jul 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - no. 239 The Case of the Generous Crook, 8 Jul 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - no. 240 The Case of the Portrait of Death, 15 Jul 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - no. 241 The Case of the Hot Briefcase, 22 Jul 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - no. 242 The Case of the Baffled Bride, 29 Jul 1951; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - no. 243 The Case of the Mother Goose Murders, 5 Aug 1951; 33 pp. (Box 332)
    - no. 244 The Case of the Hot Ice, 12 Aug 1951; 31 pp. (Box 332)
    - no. 245 The Case of the Desperate Diver, 19 Aug 1951; 31 pp. (Box 332)
    - no. 246 The Case of the Murder Memory, 26 Aug 1951; 31 pp. (Box 332)
    - no. 247 The Case of the Merry-Go-Round Murder, 2 Sep 1951; 32 pp. (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Warehouse Murders, 9 Sep 1951; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Impossible Crime, 16 Sep 1951; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Browbeaten Brain, 23 Sep 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Murder on the Mound, 30 Sep 1951; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Vengeful Gangster, 7 Oct 1951; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Blindman's Bluff, 14 Oct 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Five Hundred Suspects, 21 Oct 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Kidnapped Train, 28 Oct 1951; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 332)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Baffling Bell, 4 Nov 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Skid Row Murders, 11 Nov 1951; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Kidnapped Bus, 18 Nov 1951; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Wounded Clock, 25 Nov 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Vanishing Roadhouse, 2 Dec 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Murdering Major, 9 Dec 1951; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Borrowed Timers, 16 Dec 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Invisible Star, 23 Dec 1951; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Twin Murders, 30 Dec 1951; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Bootleg Dog, 6 Jan 1952; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Red Moon, 13 Jan 1952; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Ambitious Silversmith, 20 Jan 1952; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Folsom Point, 27 Jan 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Mathematical Crook, 3 Feb 1952; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Three Times Murder, 10 Feb 1952; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Murder by the Dozen, 17 Feb 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Champlain-12, 24 Feb 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 333)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the 15 Story Murder, 2 Mar 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Bloodstained Alibi, 9 Mar 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Cautious Colonel, 16 Mar 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Frosted Window, 23 Mar 1952; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Malacca Cane, 30 Mar 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Mysterious Mr. X, 6 Apr 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Impulsive Killer, 13 Apr 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Lost Star, 20 Apr 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Freeze-Out, 27 Apr 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Deadly Diamonds, 4 May 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Blue Madonna, 11 May 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Mama Joe, Junk Dealer, 18 May 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Red Dragon, 25 May 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Mr. Bluebird, 1 Jun 1952; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Beautiful Corpse, 8 Jun 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Oxford Needles, 15 Jun 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Forty Fishermen, 22 Jun 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 334)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Phantom Fortune, 29 Jun 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Recipe for Murder, 6 Jul 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Curious Cat, 13 Jul 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Lying Corpse, 20 Jul 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Lying Widow, 27 Jul 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Ironclad Alibi, 3 Aug 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Death Assignment, 10 Aug 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Vanishing Gun, 17 Aug 1952; "Recorded Jul 27, 1952"; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Tired Bullet, 24 Aug 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Caribbean Cruise, 31 Aug 1952; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Man Who Paid Twice, 7 Sep 1952; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Devil's Dishpan, 14 Sep 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Mailbox Murder, 21 Sep 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Murder Museum, 28 Sep 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Rehearsal For Death, 5 Oct 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Unwelcome Guest, 12 Oct 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Reformed Delinquent, 19 Oct 1952; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 335)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Decoy Store, 26 Oct 1952; 26 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Merry Little Men, 2 Nov 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Box of Rouge, 9 Nov 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Counterfeit Face, 16 Nov 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the King-Sized Frame, 23 Nov 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Little Black Book, 30 Nov 1952; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Murder Memoirs, 7 Dec 1952; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Whistling Corpse, 14 Dec 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Blazing Diamonds, 21 Dec 1952; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Wrong Spot, 28 Dec 1952; 23 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Prescription for Death, 4 Jan 1953; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Invisible Man, 11 Jan 1953; 22 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Nightmare That Came True, 18 Jan 1953; 22 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Anonymous Corpse, 25 Jan 1953; 23 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Green Corduroy Bandit, 1 Jan 1953; 24 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Firebug Murder, 8 Feb 1953; 23 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Golden Gods, 15 Feb 1953; 28 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Style-Show Sapphires, 22 Feb 1953; 25 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Purloined Pussycat, 1 Mar 1953; 25 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Jalopy Jinx, 8 Mar 1953; 25 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Echoing Clue, 15 Mar 1953; 26 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Golden Cow, 22 Mar 1953; 27 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Unlikely Grave, 29 Mar 1953; 24 pp. (Box 336)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Impossible Murder, 5 Apr 1953; 22 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Body in the Well, 12 Apr 1953; 23 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Useless Engagement Ring, 19 Apr 1953; 23 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Dangerous Alibi, 26 Apr 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Red-Headed Herring, 3 May 1953; 23 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Fly Leaf Murder, 10 May 1953; 25 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Visiting Vampire, 17 May 1953; 24 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Murderous Booby Traps, 24 May 1953; 24 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Short Snorter, 31 May 1953; 22 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Unlucky Horseshoe, 7 Jun 1953; 24 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Desert Drowning, 14 Jun 1953; 29 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Man Who Got Away with Murder, 21 Jun 1953; 23 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Diamond Trail, 28 Jun 1953; 24 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Phantom Accident, 5 Jul 1953; 28 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Walking Corpse, 12 Jul 1953; 23 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Elusive Juggler, 19 Jul 1953; 31 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Wheel Chair Murder, 26 Jul 1953; "Recorded Jul 8, 1953"; 24 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Well-Dressed Scarecrow, 2 Aug 1953; "Recorded Jul 15, 1953"; 25 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Fabulous Fiddle, 9 Aug 1953; 27 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Green Feather Clue, 16 Aug 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Would-Be Ghost, 23 Aug 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Rodeo Murders, 30 Aug 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Stolen Elephant, 6 Sep 1953; 27 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Right Mistake, 13 Sep 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Curious Bullet Holes, 20 Sep 1953; 27 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Murder by Proxy, 4 Oct 1953; 27 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Rodeo Murder, 11 Oct 1953; 27 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Lead Pipe Cinch, 18 Oct 1953; 26 pp. (Box 337)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Deadly Doll-House, 25 Oct 1953; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Voluntary Victim, 1 Nov 1953; 22 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Comedian's Contract, 8 Nov 1953; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Dead Client, 15 Nov 1953; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Quiet Murder, 22 Nov 1953; some pages marked as "Nov 23"; 21 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Hit-and-Run Ghost, 29 Nov 1953; 22 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Clever Old Lady, 6 Dec 1953; 22 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Old Servant's Ghost, 13 Dec 1953; one copy labeled "Master copy"; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Tinted Target, 20 Dec 1953; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Cuff Link Murder, 27 Dec 1953; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Comeback Kid, 3 Jan 1954; 25 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Well Planned Murder, 10 Jan 1954; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Death on Display, 17 Jan 1954; one copy labeled "Master copy"; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Stage-Struck Heiress, 24 Jan 1954; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Professional Widow, 31 Jan 1954; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Smiling Corpse, 7 Feb 1954; 21 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Ski Lodge Murders, 14 Feb 1954; 22 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Death in Lovers Lane, 21 Feb 1954; "Master copy"; 25 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Deadly Double, 28 Feb 1954; 24 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Dangerous Flirt, 7 Mar 1954; "Master copy"; 25 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Frogman Murder, 14 Mar 1954; one copy labeled "Master copy"; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Practical Joker, 21 Mar 1954; one copy labeled "Master copy"; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Auction Murder, 28 Mar 1954; "Master copy"; 26 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Baby-Faced Killer, 4 Apr 1954; "Master copy"; 26 pp. (Box 338)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Dangerous Memory, 11 Apr 1954; 25 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Waldo's Widow, 18 Apr 1954; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Talking Clock, 25 Apr 1954; 28 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Death in Deep Water, 2 May 1954; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Guilty Heart, 9 May 1954; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Haunted Burial Grave, 16 May 1954; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Accusing Blood, 23 May 1954; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Jealous Witch, 30 May 1954; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Million Dollar Motive, 6 Jun 1954; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Deadly Lifeguard, 13 Jun 1954; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Eager Witness, 20 Jun 1954; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of the Rod and Reel Murder, 27 Jun 1954; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] The Case of Waldo the Witness, 11 Jul 1954; "Recorded Jun 12, 1954"; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - [unnumbered] Case of the Girl on the Loose, 31 Oct 1954; "Recorded Oct 25, 1954"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 339)
    - no. 6 Murder by Reflection, 7 Nov 1954; "Recorded Nov 7, 1954"; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. [7] Ghost Train, 14 Nov 1954; "Recorded Nov 9, 1954"; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 8 The Case of Charlie Mahoney, 21 Nov 1954; "Recorded Nov 16, 1954"; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 9 The Man Who Wasn't There, 28 Nov 1954; "Recorded Nov 23, 1954"; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 10 The Framing of Dixie Schultz, 5 Dec 1954; "Recorded Nov 30, 1954"; 27 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. [11] The Frustrated Ego, 12 Dec 1954; "Recorded Dec 8, 1954"; 31 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 12 The Case of the Man from Suez, 19 Dec 1954; "Recorded Dec 14, 1954"; 30 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 13 The Case of the Little Man Who Cried, 26 Dec 1954; "Recorded Dec 21, 1954"; 32 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 14 The Case of the Perilous Switch, 2 Jan 1955; "Recorded Dec 28, 1954"; 31 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. [15] The Case of the Hijackers, 9 Jan 1955; "Recorded Jan 4, 1955"; 32 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 16 The Case of the Pact with the Devil, 16 Jan 1955; "Recorded Jan 11, 1955"; 34 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 17 The Case of the Girl on the Run, 23 Jan 1955; "Recorded Jan 17, 1955"; 32 pp. (Box 340)
    - no. 18 The Case of the Man with the Dark Eyes, 30 Jan 1955; "Recorded Jan 24, 1955"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 19 The Option on a Wife, 6 Feb 1955; "Recorded Jan 31, 1955"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 20 Case of the Righteous Hoodlum, 13 Feb 1955; "Recorded Feb 7, 1955"; 35 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. [21] The Case of the Constant Telephone, 20 Feb 1955; "Recorded Feb 14, 1955"; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 22 The Case of the Corpse that Moved, 27 Feb 1955; "Recorded Feb 21, 1955"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 340)
    - no. 23 Without a Face, 6 Mar 1955; "Recorded Feb 21, 1955"; 36 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [24] The Case of the Mountain Secret, 13 Mar 1955; "Recorded Feb 28, 1955"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [25] The Bootleg Ivory Runner, 20 Mar 1955; "Recorded Mar 7, 1955"; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [26] The Three Headed Yama, 27 Mar 1955; "Recorded Mar 14, 1955"; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 27 The Case of Marty Jones, 3 Apr 1955; "Recorded Mar 21, 1955"; 36 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 28 The Case of Lupo Moreno, 10 Apr 1955; "Recorded Mar 28, 1955"; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [29] Case of the Baron Leopold, 17 Apr 1955; "Recorded Apr 4, 1955"; 33 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [30] The Case of the Circus Fire, 24 Apr 1955; "Recorded Apr 11, 1954"; 34 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 31 The Case of the Missing Code Book, 1 May 1955; "Recorded Apr 18, 1954"; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [32] The Case of the Three Sided Knife, 8 May 1955; "Recorded Apr 25, 1954"; 31 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. [33] The Case of the Roads That Crossed, 15 May 1955; "Recorded May 2, 1954"; 29 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 34 The Case of John Ignacius Pilgrim, 22 May 1955; "Recorded May 11, 1954; 32 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 35 The Case of the Voodoo Drums, 29 May 1955; 30 pp.; 2 copies (Box 341)
    - no. 36 The Case of the Framing of Nick Carter, 5 Jun 1955; "Recorded May 23, 1955"; 31 pp. (Box 341)
    - no. 37 The Case of the Missing Bride, 12 Jun 1955; "Recorded May 31, 1955"; 36 pp.; 2 copies (Box 342)